[ { "front": "I am",
		"back": "io sono" },
	{ "front": "you are",
		"back": "tu sei" },
	{ "front": "he is",
		"back": "lui è" },
	{ "front": "she is",
		"back": "lei è" },
	{ "front": "we are",
		"back": "noi siamo" },
	{ "front": "you(s) are",
		"back": "voi seite" },
	{ "front": "they are",
		"back": "loro sono" },
	{ "front": "to be",
		"back": "essere" },
	{ "front": "<u>to be</u><ul style=\"list-style-type:none\"><li>i am</li><li>you are</li><li>she is</li><li>they are</li><li>we are</li><li>you are</li></ul>",
		"back": "<u>essere</u><ul style=\"list-style-type:none\"><li>io sono</li><li>tu sei</li><li>lei è</li><li>loro sono</li><li>noi siamo</li><li>voi seite</li></ul>" },
	{ "front": "to have",
		"back": "avere" },
	{ "front": "I have",
		"back": "io ho" },
	{ "front": "you have",
		"back": "tu hai" },
	{ "front": "she has",
		"back": "lei ha" },
	{ "front": "he has",
		"back": "lui ha" },
	{ "front": "they have",
		"back": "loro hanno" },
	{ "front": "we have",
		"back": "noi abbiamo" },
	{ "front": "you(s) have",
		"back": "voi avete" },
  { "front": "<u>to go</u><ul style=\"list-style-type:none\"><li>i go</li><li>you go</li><li>he goes</li><li>they go</li><li>we go</li><li>you go</li></ul>",
    "back": "<u>andare</u><ul style=\"list-style-type:none\"><li>io vado</li><li>tu vai</li><li>lui va</li><li>loro vanno</li><li>noi andiamo</li><li>voi andate</li></ul>" }
]
